<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<posts>
  <row Id="1" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:12:34.090" Score="26" ViewCount="25664" Body="&lt;p&gt;What open source miner applications are there? Especially to see how the mining process works.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="12" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2016-01-21T15:10:59.710" LastActivityDate="2016-01-21T15:10:59.710" Title="What open source miner applications are there?" Tags="&lt;mining-setup&gt;&lt;miner-configuration&gt;&lt;mining-software&gt;" AnswerCount="10" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="8" />
  <row Id="2" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="15" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:14:50.327" Score="9" ViewCount="5052" Body="&lt;p&gt;GPU mining is the way to go, as at August 2011, until something better arrives on the market. There are plenty of GPUs out there, but only a handful offer the best performance when comparing total number of Bitcoins generated vs. power consumed vs. initial purchase cost of the chip.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Which GPUs provide the best performance in regards to Bitcoin Generation vs. Power Consumption?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="16" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2016-01-21T15:15:41.977" LastActivityDate="2016-01-21T15:15:41.977" Title="Best GPUs for Mining" Tags="&lt;mining-hardware&gt;&lt;gpu-mining&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="3" FavoriteCount="0" ClosedDate="2014-08-10T23:28:43.510" />
  <row Id="3" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:14:52.000" Score="7" ViewCount="3686" Body="&lt;p&gt;We all know that mining is supposed to keep the Bitcoin system secure. However, difficulty has risen so much that costs for power currently outstrip possible revenue for mining for a large portion of hardware - not only CPUs, but also many GPUs. Essentially for everything but specially built mining rigs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That is, if you don't take transaction fees into account. Are they already high enough to support mining? Or are mining rigs going to be enough to keep Bitcoin secure?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;edit: the question is about the current situation, not some arbitrary point in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2016-01-20T21:08:13.797" LastActivityDate="2016-01-20T21:08:13.797" Title="Is mining still profitable?" Tags="&lt;mining-reward&gt;&lt;mining-profitability&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="4" FavoriteCount="4" ClosedDate="2011-08-31T02:21:39.493" />
  <row Id="4" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:17:45.367" Score="15" Body="&lt;p&gt;The official list is on &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Software#Mining_apps&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;The Wiki&lt;/a&gt; and is constantly being modified since new software shows up fairly often, but here's the quick breakdown:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Poclbm - Python/OpenCL GPU miner (GUI)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;DiabloMiner - Java/OpenCL GPU miner (MAC OS X GUI)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;RPC Miner - remote RPC miner (MAC OS X GUI)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Phoenix miner - miner&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cpu Miner - miner&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ufasoft miner - miner&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Pyminer - Python miner, reference implementation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Remote miner - mining pool software&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Open Source FGPA Bitcoin Miner - a miner that makes use of an FPGA Board&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/m0mchil/poclbm/archives/master&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Poclbm&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://xp-dev.com/svn/phoenix-miner/files/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Phoenix&lt;/a&gt; are probably the most popular (links go to the sources) though that's based more on my opinion than any facts or studies. In either case, both should shed some light on the mining process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditDate="2015-07-28T08:25:34.603" LastActivityDate="2015-07-28T08:25:34.603" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="5" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:18:00.607" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=6458.0&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Phoenix&lt;/a&gt; is a very good GPU miner. While I couldn't find the exact license, it's source is available on GitHub: &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=6458.0&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=6458.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well, it's written in python, so you could see the source anyways. However, it's actually quite easy to understand and modify, e.g. to create your own logging interface.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:18:00.607" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="6" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:18:15.337" Score="15" Body="&lt;p&gt;jzgarzik wrote a very basic miner in Python. It is slow on purpose, because it shows how a simple miner works (and the mining process). It can also be reused as boilerplate code (the getwork JSON-RPC command).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jgarzik/pyminer/blob/master/pyminer.py&quot;&gt;https://github.com/jgarzik/pyminer/blob/master/pyminer.py&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="8" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:18:15.337" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="7" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:18:17.153" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/m0mchil/poclbm&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;M0mchil's poclbm&lt;/a&gt;, written in python, hosted on github.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27" LastEditorUserId="196" LastEditDate="2013-01-28T18:02:35.893" LastActivityDate="2013-01-28T18:02:35.893" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="8" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:18:22.287" Score="13" ViewCount="577" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would like to develop a mobile Bitcoin application for the Android and iPhone platforms.  What libraries and resources can I use?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="21" LastEditorUserId="25" LastEditDate="2011-08-30T21:32:17.007" LastActivityDate="2012-03-27T05:28:21.600" Title="How do I develop mobile applications for Bitcoin?" Tags="&lt;mobile&gt;&lt;development&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="2" />
  <row Id="9" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:18:25.467" Score="22" ViewCount="2371" Body="&lt;p&gt;I didn't get it. Should my wallet be online? What if it becomes corrupted before I make a backup? Can I use my backup wallet that was backed up few days ago?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="12" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2014-10-22T09:44:21.370" LastActivityDate="2014-10-22T09:44:21.370" Title="What happens when someone sends bitcoin to my wallet?" Tags="&lt;transactions&gt;&lt;wallet&gt;&lt;backup&gt;&lt;receiving&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="10" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:19:09.740" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Poclbm&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Poclbm&lt;/a&gt;: An open source, python based GPU miner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=9047.0&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Open Source FPGA Miner&lt;/a&gt;: The name says it all.  Hit the source for the project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="16" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:19:09.740" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="11" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:20:27.337" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;If I had more disposable income right now, I'd be investing another mining rig.  I have faith in bitcoin and want to support it, but sadly 2.2 Ghash/s is all I can contribute right now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:20:27.337" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="12" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:20:27.893" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;The most obvious open-source mining application is the official Bitcoin client itself, available at: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoin/bitcoin&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://github.com/bitcoin/bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The source code is well written and shows quite clearly the way that hashing is performed in order to mine new blocks. It is however a CPU-only algorithm, and doesn't use some of the more advanced mechanisms for accelerating the hashing process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Despite this, it definitely offers a good introduction into how the generation of blocks, hashing etc. works, without the added overhead of having to deal with potentially unfamiliar GPU-based mining code, which is intentially highly optimised and as a result will likely to be more difficult to understand, and make the basic concepts more difficult to follow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:20:27.893" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="13" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="27" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:20:47.390" Score="18" ViewCount="2645" Body="&lt;p&gt;What would the effects be on the world economy if several million people around the world would utilize the Bitcoin currency for their daily transactions? Would you expect the GDP to grow faster or slower and why?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am interested in this, because the first thing I want to get straight is whether I would contribute something positive if I supported the project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="6" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2014-10-22T09:48:12.700" LastActivityDate="2014-10-22T09:48:12.700" Title="Effect on economy if Bitcoin was widely adopted" Tags="&lt;economy&gt;&lt;adoption&gt;&lt;macroeconomics&gt;" AnswerCount="10" CommentCount="7" FavoriteCount="6" />
  <row Id="14" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="9" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:20:58.183" Score="11" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's actually quite simple. Your wallet is a collection of private keys, each identified by an ID. When someone sends you bitcoins, those are just assigned to one of those private keys. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The information about which key has how many bitcoins is stored in the bitcoin network itself, ie in the database each client has.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now if you want to use the bitcoins which belong to one specific key, you need this key to sign the transaction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So no, you don't need to be online to receive a transaction. You can also restore an older backup, as long as you haven't created any new keys in the meantime. If you have created new keys, it all depends on your luck - was the transaction sent to a new or an old key?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And if it gets corrupted before you make a backup you are SOL - nobody has the correct private key then.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:20:58.183" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="15" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:21:38.053" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Mining_hardware_comparison&quot;&gt;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Mining_hardware_comparison&lt;/a&gt; the best GPU in regards to power consumption is the 5970, the tricky part is finding one of those for sale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:21:38.053" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="16" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:22:12.293" Score="27" ViewCount="1737" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've tried to read about what a Bitcoin is, how to mine, etc.  I find them to be confusing in that I don't understand the underlying factors driving Bitcoin.  Everything I've read seems to assume the reader has some knowledge of Bitcoin (even the wiki).  Where should I start?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="18" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2014-10-12T22:14:02.697" LastActivityDate="2016-10-24T17:24:50.933" Title="What are some good resources for understanding Bitcoin?" Tags="&lt;bitcoin-literature&gt;&lt;introducing-bitcoin&gt;" AnswerCount="11" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="17" />
  <row Id="17" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:22:31.547" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;Mining will probably always be profitable to someone, and there is no threat of a low global hash threatening security. It has built in checks and balances... &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:22:31.547" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="18" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="26" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:22:33.277" Score="18" ViewCount="6654" Body="&lt;p&gt;Some mining pool admins put custom data in block headers, &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=38007.0&quot;&gt;like prayers&lt;/a&gt;. How do they do that? Where can I see that data for myself?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="15" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2016-01-27T13:41:56.127" LastActivityDate="2016-01-27T13:41:56.127" Title="How can one embed custom data in block headers?" Tags="&lt;mining-pools&gt;&lt;coinbase-transaction&gt;&lt;block-header&gt;&lt;mining-theory&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="3" FavoriteCount="4" />
  <row Id="19" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="9" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:22:42.307" Score="4" Body="&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your computer does not need to be running Bitcoin to receive coins. When someone sends coins to you, it just creates a transaction that eventually gets included in the block chain (that gets downloaded by everyone running Bitcoin) ; in other words, the whole network grants you the ability to spend those coins. So you don't need to be online for this to happen.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If your wallet corrupts and you have no backup, your coins are permanently lost.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you have a recent backup, you can reuse it safely (the wallet contains a pool of new addresses, so even if you made a few transactions it will work). However, if you made lots of transactions (more than a few dozens) since your last backup, you will lose some of your coins.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="8" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:22:42.307" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="20" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:26:38.127" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is a very open-ended question and it kind of depends on how optimistic/pessimistic you may be toward the Bitcoin community and the value of the currency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A while back PC Perspective ran an article (&lt;a href=&quot;http://pcper.com/reviews/Graphics-Cards/Bitcoin-Currency-and-GPU-Mining-Performance-Comparison/Testing-Configuration-&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;located here&lt;/a&gt;) comparing various GPUs and did a very thorough analysis of the hardware that was out there and in common use for mining.  There tests found that mining can still be considerably lucrative, however, a bitcoin was going for $14.30 each, where today it's closer to the $8.50-8.75 range.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are optimistic about bitcoins, then, yes, it's worth mining and banking your coins.  If, however, you feel that the price of each coin has dropped and will most likely not go back up for a while, if at all, you may feel that it's not worth the effort.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The answer really is relative.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="16" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:26:38.127" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="21" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="18" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:26:43.510" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;There was &lt;a href=&quot;http://dankaminsky.com/2011/08/05/bo2k11/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;a very interesting talk&lt;/a&gt; at Chaos Communication Camp this year on this topic. IIRC, you can store arbitrary information in bitcoin transactions, since they actually contain &quot;programs&quot; specifying how the transaction should be verified.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Information on the 'scripting' interface can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Script&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  See section 2.3 for details on imbedding messages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9" LastEditorUserId="4774" LastEditDate="2011-08-31T01:46:50.770" LastActivityDate="2011-08-31T01:46:50.770" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="22" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="31" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:26:59.183" Score="117" ViewCount="57789" Body="&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin users frequently generate new addresses for each transaction they make, which greatly increases the number of bitcoin addresses being used to receive money.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Would it be possible (and profitable) for someone to find collisions in the bitcoin address space in order to steal money?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="5" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2016-08-19T08:07:13.680" LastActivityDate="2017-12-04T05:25:36.733" Title="Is it possible to brute force bitcoin address creation in order to steal money?" Tags="&lt;security&gt;&lt;address&gt;&lt;weaknesses&gt;&lt;key-collision&gt;" AnswerCount="11" CommentCount="6" FavoriteCount="44" />
  <row Id="24" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:27:53.190" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;The development forum of course! There is a great deal of code you could repurpose over on github. I would think android development would be easier, and maybe a good starting point.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you know C++, definitely check out the bitcoin core.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:27:53.190" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="25" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:28:09.857" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are two factors that define the profitability of mining, and they tend to change somewhat independently of one another or at least lag one another quite significantly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first factor is difficulty. Blocks should be generated every 10 minutes on average, regardless of the amount of processing power available to the network, so difficulty adjusts how hard it is to find the solution to a block. This factor is based solely on the total hashrate of the bitcoin network.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The second factor is price. Assuming we're speaking of profitability in terms of US Dollars or other fiat currencies, we have to account for our earnings in the same currency that was used to pay for our costs. To my knowledge there is not (yet) a power company that will allow you to pay your electric bill in bitcoins.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From personal experience I can say that my dedicated rigs consume about $4 worth of electricity to produce 1 BTC and if I'm lucky enough to be average my hardware will have a long enough MTBF (mean time between failures) that its cost amortized over the life of the machine will perhaps bring that up to $4.50 or $5 per coin. At today's rate of $8.69 per BTC, it is still profitable though just barely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CPU mining cannot produce at a high enough efficiency to be worth the electricity cost, and the same can likely be said for less efficient GPUs. Of course some folks don't pay per kilowatt-hour for electricity usage and for these folks ANY kind of mining is still profitable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are also a few folks on the forums selling FPGA boards which, though quite expensive up front, consume only 10-15% of the electricity of a comparable GPU. A single Xilinx Spartan6 board, for example, produces 100 MH/s at a little under 7 watts, compared to a Radeon HD 5830 which produces around 200 MH/s (without overclocking) at about 108 watts (54 watts per 100 MH/s).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:28:09.857" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="26" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="18" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:28:38.357" Score="15" Body="&lt;p&gt;When you generate a block, the generation transaction (the one that creates new coins) has an attribute called &lt;strong&gt;coinbase&lt;/strong&gt;. It's a special value you can put anything you want in to make the block unpredictable to others (and this is good).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, naturally, you can put text in this attribute, although most just put mining-related information that is not human-readable (nonce and extra-nonce).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can read this coinbase by using a patched bitcoin node that can dump blocks, for example with the &quot;dumpblock&quot; or &quot;getblockbyhash&quot; patches.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or you can just print every string in the blockchain database directly :&#xA;&lt;code&gt;strings -n 20 blk0001.dat&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example for the 1st block:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Coinbase: &lt;code&gt;04ffff001d0104455468652054696d65732030332f4a616e2f32303039204368616e63656c6c6f72206f6e206272696e6b206f66207365636f6e64206261696c6f757420666f722062616e6b73&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ASCII-translation:&#xA;&lt;code&gt;ᝣᝣᝣᝣᝣᝣᝣEThe Times 03/Jan/2009 Chancellor on brink of second bailout for banks&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is what is used by the Eligius pool ; it puts prayers in this field.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="8" LastEditorUserId="8" LastEditDate="2012-02-17T23:43:31.647" LastActivityDate="2012-02-17T23:43:31.647" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="27" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="13" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:29:41.607" Score="17" Body="&lt;p&gt;GDP would accelerate because of less transactional friction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:29:41.607" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="28" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="51" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:30:03.693" Score="43" ViewCount="8921" Body="&lt;p&gt;The standard Bitcoin client does not encrypt wallet files, so any malicious user that gains access to this file will be able to transfer all the coins to their own wallet.  Furthermore, if I lose the wallet file then I lose access to those coins.  What steps must I take to prevent loss of coins like this?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="38" LastActivityDate="2016-05-17T15:01:41.373" Title="How can I keep my wallet secure?" Tags="&lt;wallet&gt;&lt;backup&gt;&lt;security&gt;&lt;encryption&gt;" AnswerCount="9" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="22" />
  <row Id="29" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="16" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:31:33.673" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;For a detailed, yet approachable (if you know a little bit about software and cryptography) overview of how bitcoin works, read Satoshi's white paper at: &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoin.org/bitcoin.pdf&quot;&gt;http://bitcoin.org/bitcoin.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here's a hint to get you started: a bitcoin is a balance in an account.  It's not a token that is passed around.  Many digital cash systems are based on discreet tokens.  That's not the case with bitcoin.  It is a ledger system that consists of a transaction history where balances are transferred between accounts.  If you understand this before reading the paper, it might make more sense.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:31:33.673" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="30" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:32:53.790" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;For price/hash the 5830 and 5850 have been the champs for a while. The 6990 is argueably better because of depreciation... right now it is probably better to buy bitcoins instead of rigs. Or have diversity and split between the two options.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:32:53.790" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="31" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="22" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:32:59.273" Score="61" Body="&lt;p&gt;It may be &quot;theoretically&quot; possible, but in reality it's unlikely to be achieved - As in counting the number of atoms in an office building unlikely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin addresses are actually the 256-bit &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SHA-2&quot;&gt;SHA&lt;/a&gt; hash of an &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elliptic_Curve_DSA&quot;&gt;ECDSA&lt;/a&gt; public key, so any vulnerabilities in those algorithms would constitute a vulnerability in bitcoin itself. Realistically, however, breaking this level of encryption requires a huge amount of processing power. Coincidentally it requires precisely the same kind of processing power that bitcoin mining requires and in almost every scenario it would be massively more profitable to mine than to hack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edit: It's actually RIPEMD-160(SHA-256(public key)) as opposed to just SHA-256(public key) as I originally mentioned, so it's a 160-bit hash of a 256-bit hash of a public key. While the target keyspace (160 bits) is smaller thanks to this final step, it's also an additional computation that a would-be hacker must make. While the additional computational complexity doesn't even come close to canceling out the removal of 96 bits of keyspace, it should be noted that finding a collision in a 160-bit keyspace is still incredibly difficult and time consuming. More importantly, it is more difficult and time consuming than actually mining the same number of coins would be, thus making it highly unlikely anyone would even attempt such an attack - even if the equipment to make such an attack plausible in a meaningfully small span of time existed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="22" LastEditDate="2012-02-12T21:19:08.580" LastActivityDate="2012-02-12T21:19:08.580" CommentCount="17" />
  <row Id="32" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="35" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:33:40.923" Score="23" ViewCount="6992" Body="&lt;p&gt;Adam Cohen of SeatGeek &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.quora.com/Bitcoin/Is-the-cryptocurrency-Bitcoin-a-good-idea&quot;&gt;called Bitcoin a &quot;scam&quot;&lt;/a&gt;.  Other people have compared Bitcoin to a &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ponzi_scheme&quot;&gt;Ponzi&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pyramid_scheme&quot;&gt;pyramid&lt;/a&gt; scheme.  Can Bitcoin be considered a scheme to defraud people?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="44" LastEditorUserId="2306" LastEditDate="2014-09-13T19:47:29.030" LastActivityDate="2018-10-03T10:11:45.830" Title="Is Bitcoin a scam?" Tags="&lt;fraud&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="4" />
  <row Id="33" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="22" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:34:03.990" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Theoretically it is possible (but not profitable).  But in reality the amount of money you would have to spend to do it would be a lot more than what you would make.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:34:03.990" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="34" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="9" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:34:25.540" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;You should try to keep your bitcoin client online.  This allows the client to keep up with the latest transactions.  However, You can receive money while bitcoin is offline, the transaction is logged to the network and once you reconnect and catchup with all transactions your account will show the money you received.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You should keep your wallet file protected. This includes not posting it online or sharing it with anyone. You should also limit access to your computer with the wallet file.  Consider encrypting any backups of the file.  If anyone gains access to your wallet file they will always be able to spend money from it at any point if the future.  If you suspect your wallet file has been compromised create a new wallet file and transfer all of your bitcoins to the new file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your wallet file gets corrupted you can restore it from backup and tell the bitcoin client to &quot;rescan&quot; on launch (&quot;bitcoin -rescan&quot; from the command line).  This will re-parse the wallet.dat file and restore your coins.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The one exception is if you have done more then 100 transactions on new addresses since your backup.  The backup wallet file holds up to 100 addresses after you use them up bitcoin will generate new addresses.  If money is sent to those addresses, and you then restore an old wallet.dat, that old wallet will not have access to those funds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your wallet file is destroyed without a backup all the bitcoins it contains are lost forever, like lighting a dollar bill on fire.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4774" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:34:25.540" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="35" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="32" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:34:43.903" Score="31" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's important to differentiate between a scam, where a person or entity stands to profit fraudulently from others, and a high-risk investing decision, where there is potential for a person to lose significant amounts of money without being defrauded by anyone.  With that clarification, &lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin is clearly not a scam.  Like any other currency, Bitcoin is designed to be used as money, not as an investment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A Ponzi scheme is a type of confidence scam where people who think they are earning unusually high returns on an investment are actually being paid from their own money and that of later investors.   If investors try and withdraw their original investment from the Ponzi operator, the scheme collapses because no actual profits exist and there is not enough money to return the deposited amounts.  Alternatively the Ponzi operator may simply leave and take the investors' money with them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Similarly, a pyramid scheme is a type of confidence scam where people who &quot;enroll&quot; by paying a certain amount of money are made to believe they can make a large return on their investment by recruiting other people and receiving some portion of their enrollment fee.  The scheme collapses because it requires exponential growth, so it quickly runs out of new people to enroll.  The person starting the pyramid scam, who didn't have to pay an enrollment fee, makes money off of all their referrals; while the people at the bottom parts of the pyramid, who cannot find anyone new to refer, are left with no return.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unlike either of these situations, Bitcoin has no person &quot;at the top&quot; who collects money paid for bitcoins, or has to pay out when bitcoins are sold.  Neither is there any kind of scheme in Bitcoin to harvest money off of unsuspecting people in complicated ways.  Instead, bitcoins are bought and sold on public exchanges amongst members of the general public who must all obey the same rules.  If someone has told you that Bitcoin is a moneymaking scheme, they have misconstrued it--&lt;strong&gt;bitcoins follow the same economic model as any other finite commodity and over time will tend to approach a price that reflects the value people ascribe to being able to use them&lt;/strong&gt;.  People who have made money off of buying and/or selling bitcoins are either lucky or have correctly predicted an increase in demand for them.  People who earn bitcoins through &quot;mining&quot; are being paid for verifying and securing network transactions in a highly competitive market.  In neither case is any kind of fraudulent activity or confidence scam happening.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Despite the fact that Bitcoin itself is not a scam, caution is strongly advised when entering into transactions with untrusted entities.  As with any other valuable commodity, there are many people willing to separate your bitcoins from you in sneaky or fraudulent ways.  Remember that for all practical purposes Bitcoin works just like cash.  Bitcoin Ponzi and pyramid schemes do exist and if you fall prey to them you will suffer the consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, bitcoins are a very new and unproven type of money.  Because their value depends on how widely they are accepted, they are susceptible to the same types of economic bubbles as any other commodity that is surging in popularity. The Bitcoin software is still in beta, and bitcoins should be considered &quot;high-risk&quot; from a financial perspective.  &lt;strong&gt;You should not invest money into bitcoins or Bitcoin-related technologies unless you can afford to lose it!&lt;/strong&gt;  Even firm believers in Bitcoin tend to think it will take a while for the value of bitcoins to stabilise, and no one knows at what value that stabilisation might occur.  Trade and transact safely!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="44" LastEditorUserId="27232" LastEditDate="2015-08-14T03:29:33.753" LastActivityDate="2015-08-14T03:29:33.753" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="36" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="90" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:35:09.083" Score="10" ViewCount="720" Body="&lt;p&gt;The nice thing about bitcoin is that it generates partially anonymous data about every single transaction. Can this data be used to gain insight about real-world markets? Or are there some fundamental differences that cannot be accounted for? If this data can be used, does anybody have any references on academic papers that use the bitcoin data?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="46" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2014-09-03T11:39:24.840" LastActivityDate="2014-09-03T11:39:24.840" Title="Can bitcoin transaction data be used to study markets?" Tags="&lt;economy&gt;&lt;academic-research&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="37" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="32" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:35:54.087" Score="-1" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's just a new method of conducting transactions, similar to paypal but impossible to reverse transactions.  People who don't understand it call it a scam, but it is not.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:35:54.087" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="38" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="13" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:36:32.900" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well, the GDP measured in bitcoins probably wouldn't grow at all, most likely it will shrink. However, that doesn't mean the economy shrinks, just that the bitcoins are increasing in worth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In deflation adjusted bitcoins, I think that the GDP will grow, and if only because micro- and international transactions are vastly simplified. However, I expect that it would also lead to a collapse of the traditional banking system, since those are superficial now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, note that a growing economy isn't necessarily positive. If you take into account that resources on earth are not infinite but limited, it becomes obvious that a stable, not growing economy (I think that's what you mean by GDP) is preferable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9" LastEditorUserId="9" LastEditDate="2011-08-30T21:45:53.947" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:45:53.947" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="40" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:37:12.003" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=17240.0&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=17240.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This link will show you how to create a secure wallet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:37:12.003" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="41" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:37:35.083" Score="19" Body="&lt;p&gt;One method commonly in use is an &quot;offline wallet.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To generate an offline wallet, launch a bitcoin client on a known clean computer, virtual machine, or use a bootable Linux distribution like LinuxCoin. &lt;strong&gt;Make sure this system is NOT connected to the internet for this process.&lt;/strong&gt; When the bitcoin client is first launched, it generates a brand new wallet.dat file with one address. Save that wallet.dat file to a thumb drive along with a text file containing your new bitcoin address. Delete the wallet.dat from the machine once you've copied it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Any coins sent to that address are only accessible to someone holding the wallet.dat file on your thumb drive and since the computer which generated that thumb drive has never seen the internet so it's a pretty fair bet that your copy is the only copy. Send any coins you want to secure to your &quot;offline&quot; wallet's address and use your thumb drive to recover the coins when needed. Remember that once you've used the wallet on the thumb drive, it is now &quot;burned&quot; and a new one must be generated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;There is an excellent resource for wallet-securing techniques available on &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Securing_your_wallet&quot;&gt;the Bitcoin wiki&lt;/a&gt; which also covers backup methods, encryption and many other topics at far too great a length to cover in a single answer.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="22" LastEditDate="2011-09-01T20:55:15.697" LastActivityDate="2011-09-01T20:55:15.697" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="42" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:39:42.943" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin client provides RPC calls which are in JSON, you could communicate via the RPC to make your app.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="54" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:39:42.943" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="43" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="36" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:41:28.933" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is still a fledgling currency. You can see how Bitcoin lacks credibility by listening to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.npr.org/blogs/money/2011/08/24/138673630/what-is-bitcoin&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;recent publication on NPR&lt;/a&gt;. Overall there is a great deal of misinformation, and lack of credible citations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Although, there are substantial &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ics.uci.edu/~yangwang/papers/CHI08-AuthorCopy.pdf&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Virtual_economy&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;virtual currency&lt;/a&gt;, there are no published studies from accredited sources concerning bitcoin proper.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It makes for a good economics thesis, there are plenty of hypotheses to explore!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27" LastEditorUserId="27" LastEditDate="2011-08-30T21:58:05.740" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:58:05.740" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="44" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:42:05.287" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is an involved topic and the answer will change as bitcoin clients improve.  Here is what works for me...use a drive encryption solution (i.e. truecrypt) and keep your wallet.dat file on it (you'll need to read the docs about how to relocate the wallet.dat file to a different location).  I recommend using aes256 encryption.  Make sure you remember your password used to encrypt the drive.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After creating a wallet on the encrypted drive, shut down bitcoin and unmount the encrypted drive (important to avoid data corruption).  For backup, just copy the &lt;em&gt;encrypted&lt;/em&gt; drive to other devices both inside and outside your home (i.e. online storage provider).  Since the volume is encrypted with strong encryption, it will be unusable for anyone that obtains a copy and you will have multiple copies in case your hard drive crashes (just don't lose your password!).  Anytime you spend coins out of your wallet or generate new addresses, you should update your backups.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note, this solution may not protect you from viruses...you should never handle your unencrypted wallet.dat file on a computer you suspect may be infected with viruses.  There are wallet stealing viruses in the wild.  There are more advanced measures that can be taken that further mitigate the threat posed by viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:42:05.287" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="45" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:43:29.967" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;This depends quite  a bit on your cost for electricity. In general, the ATI 6990 (758 MH/s) is fastest, but it consumes quite a bit of energy. The ATI 5970 (655 MH/s) runs at 86% of the speed of a 6990, but consumes less power. If you have a limited number of slots on your motherboard with cheap electricity, choose the ATI 6990. If you have unlimited PCI-E slots and relatively expensive electricity, choose the ATI 5970.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NOTE: There is no such thing as &quot;free&quot; electricity. Someone is paying for it. If you believe you have free electricity (i.e. a dorm) it is likely that someone is paying a cost for that power.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Mining_hardware_comparison&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Mining_hardware_comparison&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="56" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:43:29.967" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="46" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:45:21.437" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;GPU Miners&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;DiabloMiner - https://github.com/Diablo-D3/DiabloMiner&#xA;&#xA;poclbm      - https://github.com/m0mchil/poclbm&#xA;&#xA;hashkill    - 64-bit http://www.gat3way.eu/poc/hashkill-0.2.4-x86_64.tgz &#xA;&#xA;              32-bit http://www.gat3way.eu/poc/hashkill-0.2.4-x86.tgz   &#xA;&#xA;Phoenix     - https://github.com/jedi95/Phoenix-Miner&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CPU Miners&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Jgarzik     - https://github.com/jgarzik/cpuminer.git&#xA;&#xA;Ufasoft     - http://ufasoft.com/open/bitcoin/&#xA;&#xA;FPGAminer   - https://github.com/progranism/Open-Source-FPGA-Bitcoin-Miner&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:45:21.437" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="48" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="16" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:46:56.067" Score="12" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weusecoins.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Weusecoins.com&lt;/a&gt; has an excellent video on the basic premise of bitcoin. Bitcoin is a very complicated platform, and really has two separate entities. There is bitcoin the currency, and bitcoin the currency ledger.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The wiki available at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bitcoin.it&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;bitcoin.it&lt;/a&gt; will give you more in depth information if the weusecoins video is too broad.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27" LastEditorUserId="132" LastEditDate="2011-09-10T23:56:28.883" LastActivityDate="2011-09-10T23:56:28.883" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="49" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:47:06.577" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are a few options available. Here are a couple:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Encryption with Winrar is secure if you use a long password with no dictionary words, both upper case and lower case letters, numbers and special characters in it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Truecrypt is more secure but most people don't have it already installed, so it's little more time to get it setup.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whatever password you use to encrypt, make sure to record it on paper, and physically store it in a couple of easy to remember and secure locations that you will not forget. Without it, you won't be able to decrypt and access your bitcoin wallet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="7" LastEditorUserId="7" LastEditDate="2011-08-30T21:52:59.833" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:52:59.833" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="50" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="36" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:47:20.450" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm not aware of any serious studies on the topic but I &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; seen folks on the forum talking about how bitcoin price seems to correlate with the google trends data on bitcoin-related searches. Compare: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.google.com/trends?q=bitcoin&amp;amp;ctab=0&amp;amp;geo=all&amp;amp;date=ytd&amp;amp;sort=0&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Google Trends&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoincharts.com/charts/mtgoxUSD#rg360ztgMzm1g60zm2g15zi1gAroonOsczi2gBBWzi3gMDXzi4gMACD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;MtGox Price&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So there's sort of a study on popularity/price ratios, though it's hardly been conducted with any sort of scientific rigor. I'd assume that there are many such studies to be found, the limits from the bitcoin side of the fence are quite few so I'd say the upper limit is your imagination.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:47:20.450" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="51" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:47:44.180" Score="16" Body="&lt;p&gt;The &quot;offline wallet&quot; method described by David Perry is a good way to securely &lt;em&gt;generate&lt;/em&gt; a bitcoin address/wallet.dat but in order to be secure from both loss and theft the first thing you will want to do is encrypt that wallet, and then make &lt;strong&gt;many&lt;/strong&gt; different copies of it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One easy way to do this is using the program &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.truecrypt.org/&quot;&gt;TrueCrypt&lt;/a&gt; as explained &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcointalk.org/?topic=5194.0&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  To summarise the contents of the link, you will use the default options in the software to create an encrypted volume, then move your &quot;wallet.dat&quot; file into it as soon as you create it on the trusted, offline computer.  This will create an encrypted copy that can be placed on a thumbdrive and then saved in multiple locations such as &lt;a href=&quot;http://mail.google.com&quot;&gt;gmail&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://db.tt/NXE7TIX&quot;&gt;dropbox&lt;/a&gt;, a physical safe, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would also &lt;em&gt;highly&lt;/em&gt; recommend testing the file once with a small amount before copying any substantial sum of bitcoins to your newly created address.  If you are satisfied with both the test and all the precautions you have taken, then transfer the rest.  You can keep your wallet secure by not accessing it frequently, so this should be used as a savings wallet and not for regular transactions.  Hope this helps!  Also, you can find an excellent overview of good wallet practices and security methods at &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Securing_your_wallet&quot;&gt;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Securing_your_wallet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="44" LastEditorUserId="44" LastEditDate="2011-08-30T22:55:02.700" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:55:02.700" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="52" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="61" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:50:20.573" Score="61" ViewCount="25890" Body="&lt;p&gt;I read some sources that say Bitcoin transactions are anonymous, some that say they are semi-anonymous, and some that say they are not anonymous at all.  In what ways are the transactions anonymous and in what ways are they not anonymous?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="38" LastActivityDate="2018-01-18T15:59:05.730" Title="How anonymous are Bitcoin transactions?" Tags="&lt;transactions&gt;&lt;privacy&gt;&lt;blockchain&gt;" AnswerCount="9" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="26" />
  <row Id="53" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="76" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:50:40.397" Score="10" ViewCount="2830" Body="&lt;p&gt;I want to create a transparent gambling/lotto site and use the block chain as entropy for lotto numbers, dice rolls, that kind of thing.  Would the transaction hash of the latest transaction be the best way to do this?  How often are transaction hashes created?  How would you, programmatically, access them?  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="58" LastEditorUserId="22837" LastEditDate="2015-02-18T09:08:11.893" LastActivityDate="2015-02-18T09:08:11.893" Title="Is there a way to use the block chain as entropy in random number generator?" Tags="&lt;block-header&gt;&lt;blockchain&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="5" FavoriteCount="1" ClosedDate="2011-09-21T00:51:01.393" />
  <row Id="54" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="16" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:51:56.637" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think that the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bitcoin.it/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Bitcoin wiki&lt;/a&gt; is actually a very good place to learn about Bitcoin. Just read the articles there. If you don't understand something, just continue reading and then follow up on the terms you didn't understand.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you then still have questions left, feel free to ask them here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PS: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weusecoins.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;we use coins&lt;/a&gt; is also a good place to start, especially the video mentioned by Matth1a3.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2015-07-28T13:59:05.193" LastActivityDate="2015-07-28T13:59:05.193" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="55" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="22" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:52:29.213" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Possible: Yes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Probable: No.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many events are possible even though they're not probable. The likelihood of bruteforcing a bitcoin private key is improbable enough that with current computing standards it is, for all intents and purposes, impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the science of cryptography develops and as bruteforcing becomes more powerful the underlying bitcoin infrastructure will be improved to keep pace with the improving technology. This may require accessing your bitcoin wallet using an improved client in the future to maintain a high standard of security.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, a bitcoin address is not the same as a private key. Generating a bitcoin address will allow an attacker to send you coins, but it would not allow them to sign transactions with your private key (i.e. remove coins from your wallet).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="56" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:52:29.213" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="56" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="32" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:52:38.333" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin is definitely not a scam.  People have opinions about whether it will or will not succeed, but it's not a scam.  It like to think of it as the first money that is designed for the internet.  There have been previous attempts at digital money, but all have relied on a central authority to solve the &quot;double spend&quot; problem.  Until the advent of bitcoin, a transaction on the internet required a third party to the transaction (for example, a bank that manages account balances).  Bitcoin, like cash, requires no third party.  Also like cash, it is an irreversible transaction and can be stolen.  Bitcoin was designed with the modern internet in mind unlike credit cards (invented in the 1950s) or ACH (invented in 1972).  Bitcoin can serve as a solid (as in secure) foundation on which many other financial instruments and innovations can be based.  The software systems that the current banking system uses are antiquated, haphazardly put together, and could not have foreseen the needs of the modern internet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:52:38.333" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="57" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:52:39.317" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;Currently there are only a few mobile apps that use the bitcoin protocol itself. Most communicate with a bitcoin client on a remote machine using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/API_reference_%28JSON-RPC%29&quot;&gt;JSON API.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Those few that do, rely on &lt;a href=&quot;http://code.google.com/p/bitcoinj/&quot;&gt;BitcoinJ&lt;/a&gt; which is a &quot;selfish&quot; implementation of bitcoin that runs in Java (handily the native language for Android apps). It's got a few key modifications that bring its overhead low enough to run on embedded devices, most notably it does not download all blocks in the block-chain, only those blocks which relate to addresses in its own wallet (hence &quot;selfish&quot; client).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Either method works, and either is as valid a starting point as the other, given the current state of bitcoin's mobile development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:52:39.317" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="58" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="52" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:53:48.897" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;They are anonymous in that we don't know the name of the physical holder of a wallet. However, the interactions in terms of wallet ids are completely public. See these questions for more details:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cstheory.stackexchange.com/q/7145/1037&quot;&gt;https://cstheory.stackexchange.com/q/7145/1037&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://crypto.stackexchange.com/q/508/617&quot;&gt;https://crypto.stackexchange.com/q/508/617&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="46" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:48:25.933" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:53:48.897" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="59" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="77" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:54:14.593" Score="43" ViewCount="26072" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would like to start mining, but my GPU isn't the greatest and I don't really want to spend the money on a dedicated rig. Is mining from my CPU (in a Linux environment) still worth it? Or will I not be able to keep up?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2016-01-21T15:22:31.887" LastActivityDate="2016-01-21T15:22:31.887" Title="Is CPU mining even worth it?" Tags="&lt;linux&gt;&lt;mining-profitability&gt;&lt;cpu-mining&gt;" AnswerCount="8" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="4" ClosedDate="2015-11-07T18:14:59.163" />
  <row Id="60" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:56:08.583" Score="3" ViewCount="480" Body="&lt;p&gt;It seems like the only way to sell BTC for products/services is to have the BTC reflect how other currencies are doing. I'm not great in economics but can it ever be stable?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="24" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2014-11-01T12:47:46.800" LastActivityDate="2014-11-01T12:57:24.237" Title="Can the price of Bitcoin ever be stable to the USD?" Tags="&lt;economy&gt;&lt;price-volatility&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="3" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="61" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="52" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:56:37.597" Score="40" Body="&lt;p&gt;Technically the appropriate term is &quot;pseudonymous&quot; - imagine that your bitcoin address is like an email address or an online alias: how hard it is to trace to your actions depend largely on what you do with it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is, for example, a bitcoin address in my forum signature that would obviously be VERY traceable back to me. On the other hand if I install the client on a separate system which only connects to the internet through TOR and obtain my bitcoins by mining them from a pool like &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Eligius&quot;&gt;Eligius&lt;/a&gt; (no accounts/email necessary, they only ask for a bitcoin address) then it would be very difficult indeed to trace those funds to me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And of course there are shades of gray in-between. As I said, think of it as being an email address and then consider how your actions with that bitcoin address can be tied to you. It's difficult but possible to make truly anonymous bitcoin transactions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:56:37.597" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="62" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="53" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:57:30.917" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Only sort of. The transaction hash is specifically chosen &lt;em&gt;because&lt;/em&gt; it is smaller than some number X (--&gt; difficulty factor), so it isn't fully random. However, it has a lot of entropy in the sense that it contains input from a lot of different, not predictable transactions. So you could use this hash as a seed for your RNG.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you just want to generate lotto numbers and dice rolls, I'd say it's more important that you find a good random number generator (RNG) - you won't reseed that often anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you wanted to use the hash as the random number directly, there's a problem: you only get one hash every ~10 minutes. Not all that many random numbers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:57:30.917" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="64" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="53" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:57:53.247" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;You could scrape data from &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoincharts.com/bitcoin/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://bitcoincharts.com/bitcoin/&lt;/a&gt; to get the hashes of transactions that had just been submitted.  It wouldn't super easy to do, but it'd be a constant source of fairly random data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:57:53.247" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="65" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="59" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:58:24.287" Score="13" Body="&lt;p&gt;It depends on your specific valuation of &quot;worth it.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By most valuations (i.e. value of BTC produced &gt; electricity costs) it is not, but if you don't pay for electricity it might be. It might also be worth it to you to mine at a loss if you truly believe that 1 BTC might be worth thousands someday.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Realistically, though, it is probably more worthwhile to simply purchase BTC at an exchange or from another user.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:58:24.287" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="66" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="74" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:58:29.643" Score="49" ViewCount="7725" Body="&lt;p&gt;With the limited total quantity of bitcoins, and people losing their wallets constantly decreasing that number, won't rampant deflation destroy Bitcoin?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="44" LastEditorUserId="5406" LastEditDate="2014-11-01T11:27:03.293" LastActivityDate="2014-11-01T11:27:03.293" Title="Will deflation destroy Bitcoin?" Tags="&lt;economy&gt;&lt;weaknesses&gt;&lt;deflation&gt;&lt;shrinking-money-supply&gt;" AnswerCount="13" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="19" />
  <row Id="67" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="60" CreationDate="2011-08-30T21:59:48.533" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin is still very new, it is unlikely that it will sit at one price for a very long period of time.  When all of the bitcoins have been mined it is much more likely to sit at a stable price.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T21:59:48.533" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="68" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="59" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:01:01.463" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;CPU mining is only worth it if you are not paying for your electricity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:01:01.463" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="69" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="52" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:01:49.980" Score="9" Body="&lt;p&gt;It is considered pseudo-anonymous.  With casual usage, it is not very anonymous at all.  Transactions occur between cryptographic addresses and anyone can create any number of these addresses.  However, Bitcoin transactions can be traced back to your IP address.  The history of all transactions can be analyzed for spatial and temporal correlations.  If one address can be linked to a person, then related transactions can be identified.  I would say that bitcoin offers a degree of privacy not offered by other means of online payment, but for a sufficiently motivated entity, it is possible to reconstruct a person's bitcoin transaction activity.  There are steps that one can take to make it more anonymous, but it is certainly not as anonymous as physical cash.  And, you have to know what you're doing to use it in complete anonymity.  I would not advise using bitcoin if you are seeking complete anonymity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:01:49.980" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="70" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="22" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:02:03.257" Score="12" Body="&lt;p&gt;No, it is not possible, for two reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, you would have to generate and hash an unimaginably large number of ECDSA keypairs to have a reasonable chance of finding a collision. With current computing power, that would take longer than the age of the universe.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Second, as pointed out in the other answers it is much more profitable to generate bitcoins if you have lots of computing power.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="53" LastEditorUserId="196" LastEditDate="2012-02-12T15:54:06.823" LastActivityDate="2012-02-12T15:54:06.823" CommentCount="15" />
  <row Id="71" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="60" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:02:07.733" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;The price is a reflection of basic market forces at work: supply and demand.  Currently relatively small transactions represent a large portion of the market, so this can naturally lead to some inefficiencies.  Nobody can know for sure whether stability will be reached, but it seems likely to me that stability will tend to increase with the number of active users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="38" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:02:07.733" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="72" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="303" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:02:20.277" Score="35" ViewCount="19515" Body="&lt;p&gt;Some services, such as &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoinlaundry.com/&quot;&gt;bitcoinlaundry.com&lt;/a&gt;, claim that they can launder your bitcoins.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since all bitcoin transactions are publicly logged, how is this done? Wouldn't it be possible to trace back the transactions and find out the initial address?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="5" LastEditorUserId="5" LastEditDate="2011-08-31T18:11:02.100" LastActivityDate="2014-06-10T13:37:02.303" Title="How is it possible to launder bitcoins?" Tags="&lt;transactions&gt;&lt;blockchain&gt;&lt;privacy&gt;&lt;address&gt;&lt;money-laundering&gt;" AnswerCount="9" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="10" />
  <row Id="73" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="52" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:02:37.150" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;They are not anonymous at all. Bitcoin is just a distributed accounting scheme - every client stores all transactions, so no secret transactions are possible. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, if there's no way to tie a specific address to you (you bought your bitcoins with cash) and no way to tie the receiver of your transaction to you (you simply donated to the EFF) then it's pseudonymous. Everybody knows that a transaction to the EFF has taken place from some address, but nobody knows it's you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:02:37.150" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="74" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="66" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:03:26.497" Score="43" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are two potential ways in which &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Deflation&quot;&gt;monetary deflation&lt;/a&gt; can impact a currency:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.  Usability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most modern currencies have a minimum unit, such as the penny in the United States, or the yen in Japan.  If these currencies existed in only finite quantities, then as the economy grew and/or physical money was lost, there might eventually be too few of these units in circulation to allow normal commerce.  Imagine if, for example, the U.S. dollar became so rare that you could buy a car with a single U.S. penny.  How would you buy a loaf of bread?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin, however, does not have this problem because unlike the physical currencies of most countries, bitcoins are infinitely divisible.  Even if only one bitcoin remained, it would be sufficient to run a substantial economy on, based on the ability to use tiny fractions of it like the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/FAQ#What_do_I_call_the_various_denominations_of_Bitcoins.3F&quot;&gt;Satoshi&lt;/a&gt;.  If even the Satoshi were to become too highly valued/unavailable for commerce, the Bitcoin protocol could be updated to allow even smaller denominations.  So the usability of bitcoins is safe from the effects of deflation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Broader economic consequences from deflation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many economists believe that deflation is bad for an economy because people will be less likely to invest their money if they can &quot;earn&quot; increased value simply by holding on to it.  Why buy something today, the argument goes, if you could buy it for half as much in a few months time?  Also, taking out loans becomes very difficult, because to be practical they have to have negative interest rates and then why would anyone loan out money in the first place?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, there is good reason to believe that deflation might not have such a negative effect on Bitcoin.  For one, Bitcoin is unlikely to become the only currency in the world economy, so investments, loans, etc. can simply be denominated in another currency.  But even more importantly there are several concrete examples from history of strictly deflationary currencies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Swiss_dinar&quot;&gt;Iraqi &quot;Swiss&quot; dinar&lt;/a&gt; was a currency that ceased being printed after the first Gulf War, and was left in use only by the Kurdish regions of the country.  With a finite number of &quot;Swiss&quot; dinars in existence, and some being lost or damaged over time, this left the currency in precisely the same state as Bitcoin.  Since it was no longer backed by a government, many economists expected the currency and its economy to collapse.  Instead, the Kurdish economy continued largely as normal for 13 years, and the &quot;Swiss&quot; dinar even appreciated against the &quot;Saddam&quot; dinar that was meant to replace it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://falkvinge.net/2011/08/21/bitcoins-deflationary-economy-not-a-problem-in-itself/&quot;&gt;Rick Falkvinge&lt;/a&gt; also raises another excellent point regarding deflationary economies.  If, as economists expect, people would decline to buy something today as opposed to next year for half price, then it should be the case that no one ever buys computers, right?  But in fact, the computer industry thrives despite this continued trend of &quot;whatever something costs today, it will cost a fraction of that within a few years&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, this is a question for economists to duke out, and you can find more information about how different economic schools approach the problem &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=11627.0&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  Suffice it to say, this cannot be considered a crippling fault in Bitcoin as a technology.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="44" LastEditorUserId="44" LastEditDate="2011-10-05T18:50:45.327" LastActivityDate="2011-10-05T18:50:45.327" CommentCount="8" />
  <row Id="75" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:03:42.857" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;The upcoming Bitcoin client v0.4 will have encryption on wallet.dat if you choose to set password on wallet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="54" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:03:42.857" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="76" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="53" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:04:03.027" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=9812.0&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Lottery&lt;/a&gt; used an SHA256 hash of the two most recent blocks to generate random data and to my recollection there were not too many complaints about that method they chose. In any case it's only good for 256 bits of questionably random data every 10 minutes (20 if you don't reuse blocks) so there are probably better entropy sources, such as the setup they've built over at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.random.org/&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot;&gt;random.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:04:03.027" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="77" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="59" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:04:16.000" Score="24" Body="&lt;p&gt;For the amount of time you would spend setting up a CPU miner, at minimum wage in the US you would be at a loss.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even GPU mining is barely profitable for most people right now. It would definitely be more profitable to speculate, and even more profitable to operate a Bitcoin business. There are a great deal of people who want to use their Bitcoins for purchases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the current exchange of under $10:1BTC, the most efficient graphics cards are taking months to pay off their initial investment (with free electricity).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:04:16.000" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="78" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="60" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:06:13.820" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;No currencies are stable unless they have a central bank making it artificially stabile. When that is said, the stability will largely be depending on the size of the economy. I do not, however know exactly how to measure the size of the Bitcoin economy, but I assume it should be measured in terms of the total amount sent between people or companies over a period of time (which would be similar to the measurement of GDP). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="6" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:06:13.820" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="79" PostTypeId="7" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:07:11.680" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;The Bitcoin stack exchange is for users and enthusiasts of Bitcoin and related technologies.  If you have a question about …&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;how to use or accept bitcoins&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the Bitcoin network or protocol&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the open-source &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoin.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Bitcoin client&lt;/a&gt; or other Bitcoin software&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;a cryptocurrency or technology derived directly from Bitcoin such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Namecoin&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Namecoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;distributed cryptocurrencies not derived directly from Bitcoin such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Ripple&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and it is &lt;strong&gt;not about&lt;/strong&gt; …&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;programming technique&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;investment advice&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;politics or philosophy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;a site or software recommendation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;then you’re in the right place to ask your question!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="-1" LastEditorUserId="22" LastEditDate="2013-02-13T17:17:09.817" LastActivityDate="2013-02-13T17:17:09.817" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="80" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="72" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:09:12.620" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;You get bitcoins from 2 or more sources and give their bitcoins to each other.  Now expand that and do it many times and you can launder bitcoins.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:09:12.620" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="81" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="72" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:09:37.557" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you purchase a bunch of Bitcoins with dirty money, and then sell the Bitcoins for clean money - you have essentially laundered your money with Bitcoins. You can then claim that your income came from Bitcoin mining, and it would be difficult to investigate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is exceedingly difficult to anonymize your Bitcoin transactions. I think the appeal is that it adds an extra hoop for the IRS to jump through.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not only is it possible and &lt;a href=&quot;http://anonymity-in-bitcoin.blogspot.com/2011/07/bitcoin-is-not-anonymous.html&quot;&gt;proven&lt;/a&gt; that people can trace transaction origins, but it will likely be easier to do in the future if the Bitcoin core remains unchanged in this respect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin anonymity is a fallacy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:09:37.557" CommentCount="7" />
  <row Id="82" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="72" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:10:14.200" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;It will always be possible to trace a transaction back to its initial wallet. This is a design choice by the Bitcoin team, and could have been avoided (see the &lt;a href=&quot;https://crypto.stackexchange.com/q/508/617&quot;&gt;answers to this question&lt;/a&gt; for more). However, there could be some legal ways of avoiding this, because if they money goes through several wallets, even if you can't hide the wallets, you could deny ownership of the earlier ones, and argue that this was a random gift somebody gave to you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="46" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:48:25.933" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:10:14.200" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="83" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:10:28.057" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;CPU miner in PHP - &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/codler/Bitcoin-phpMiner&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://github.com/codler/Bitcoin-phpMiner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="54" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:10:28.057" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="84" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="66" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:11:28.057" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's been a long time since my Econ101 class but let's see if I can get this right...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deflation of the currency is only an issue in two circumstances, neither of which currently apply to bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Deflation harms individuals who have large debts in the deflating currency, especially those with fixed payments. If the value of one dollar doubles tomorrow then a $1,000 mortgage payment suddenly seems quite a lot to pay for a property that was entirely worth that sum not long ago.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Deflation harms individuals when the lag time between the deflation and price changes is substantial or when companies hold large amounts of stocks purchased at pre-inflation prices and are unwilling to sell at a &quot;loss&quot; even though the money is now worth more.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To my knowledge, no one is making or taking out substantial loans denominated in BTC with fixed payment plans, though that may soon change. There are also many discussions on the forums and elsewhere regarding how loans denominated in BTC might be made more feasible in a deflationary system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for #2, there are few (if any) companies who hold stock purchased with BTC and sell at fixed BTC prices. Almost all companies have stock purchased with fiat currency and their pricing is automatically updated at the time of sale to reflect a fiat value, so they do not face the &quot;selling at a 'loss'&quot; scenario.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:11:28.057" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="85" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="111" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:13:42.560" Score="14" ViewCount="7489" Body="&lt;p&gt;What is it that makes Bitcoin unique amongst crypto-currencies?  Is it just the most popular one or does it have better design aspects too?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="67" LastActivityDate="2017-09-01T05:17:16.523" Title="What are the differences between Bitcoin and other crypto-currencies?" Tags="&lt;currencies&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="86" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:13:47.620" Score="13" ViewCount="2130" Body="&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gini_coefficient&quot;&gt;Gini coefficient&lt;/a&gt; is a measure of the inequality of something's distribution, where a value of 0 represents total equality and a value of 1 maximal inequality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is it possible to perform this type of estimate on how bitcoins are distributed throughout the userbase? And/or is it possible to tell how this distribution is changing over time? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastEditorUserId="44" LastEditDate="2011-08-31T23:43:12.943" LastActivityDate="2019-05-15T12:11:10.470" Title="Is it possible to estimate the Gini coefficient for Bitcoins and if the trend is increasing or decreasing?" Tags="&lt;economics&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="7" FavoriteCount="2" />
  <row Id="87" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:13:56.973" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I use virtual machine with encrypted home folder. It's a bit geeky, but is very secure and I am able to send money with no hassle of repeating the process (David Perry's advice). Don't forget to encrypt and backup your wallet.dat regularly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With time there will be many reputable online wallet services available, though I would recommend diversifying your bitcoins in multiple places, just in case.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="23" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:13:56.973" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="88" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="110" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:16:20.563" Score="16" ViewCount="1916" Body="&lt;p&gt;As I understand things, the security and integrity of Bitcoin rely on the assumption that its hashing is &quot;hard&quot; in some sense.  However, in the past, processing power has increased exponentially.  This has made some problems solvable in a reasonable amount of time that were not solvable before.  How does Bitcoin account for the possibility that processing power will continue to increase in the future?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="38" LastEditorUserId="5" LastEditDate="2011-09-02T16:23:01.833" LastActivityDate="2011-09-02T16:23:01.833" Title="Is Bitcoin future-proof?" Tags="&lt;security&gt;&lt;hash&gt;&lt;future-proof&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="5" FavoriteCount="6" />
  <row Id="89" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="66" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:16:35.130" Score="14" Body="&lt;p&gt;No.  There are many things that could destroy bitcoin, but deflation is not one of them.  While deflation is problematic for a currency backed by debt (as most, if not all, national currencies are), it is not an issue for commodity currencies (and bitcoin is most similar to commodity currencies).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The deflation argument goes something like this: everyone, believing that the value of the currency is going to rise will simply hold the currency and never spend it.  But this argument completely ignores the need for diversification (would you put all of your wealth into bitcoin?).  It also ignores the fact that if people decided to put all their wealth into bitcoin and save everything, they would still need to eat and buy things at some point.  They would have no choice but to spend it.  And, if everyone actually did invest everything into bitcoin, it would create a bubble in the value that would eventually deflate and teach everyone why diversification is good.  The argument also ignores the fact that hoarding itself is not bad...when people hoard bitcoin, they cause the value to rise and that creates wealth that others can use for their needs.  In a way, hoarding is an investment in the broad bitcoin economy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:16:35.130" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="90" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="36" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:19:16.503" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are no academic papers on Bitcoin market behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If Bitcoin or another peer-to-peer currency ever develops a significant closed economy, then it would be a rich source of information on the behavior of markets and economies, as the transaction timing, value and locations (for both the sender and receiver in a transaction) of Bitcoin transactions is publicly broadcasted -and in the case of timing and value, already being recorded in the block chain. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, information about the full Bitcoin transaction history of each pseudonymous individual can be deduced through network analysis techniques.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While Bitcoin is reserved for niche use and doesn't form a closed economy though, the data from the transaction history is of limited use for studying real world market and economic behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, in the future the visibility of Bitcoin transaction data could be reduced if many participants in the Bitcoin economy begin to rely on private layers built on top of the Bitcoin network to conduct their transactions through, which is likely to happen given the implications for privacy that visible transactions create.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="7" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:19:16.503" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="91" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="100" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:20:32.367" Score="119" ViewCount="48435" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a question many people ask when they're introduced to Bitcoin.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin sounds interesting, but if I want to use this system I will need to get some coins, otherwise, there's no way I can spend them! How can I start?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastEditorUserId="63569" LastEditDate="2018-03-09T14:16:45.353" LastActivityDate="2019-05-08T20:17:01.650" Title="How do you obtain bitcoins?" Tags="&lt;trading&gt;&lt;buy-bitcoins&gt;&lt;mining-reward&gt;" AnswerCount="9" CommentCount="4" FavoriteCount="44" />
  <row Id="92" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="102" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:22:12.410" Score="18" ViewCount="704" Body="&lt;p&gt;Great effort has been put into Bitcoin's concept of money supply and that there will never be more than 21 million units.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, it's relatively easy to fork it and create alternate block chains. SolidCoin, IXCoin, IOCoin etc are much less worth, but they can easily be traded against Bitcoin. Does this increase the over-all supply of Bitcoin-like money to well beyond 21 million units? Some believe yes, and that this is one reason already for the recent price drop.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, the concept of open and decentralized P2P money is still young. Chances are that a lot of other such currencies will pop up in time. Is there a risk that Bitcoin will be thwarted by an inflation of other currencies, rendering it and all other open, &quot;free&quot;, decentralized money worthless and useless?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;EDIT: One thing to consider in this context is that the number of traditional currencies will always be limited as there are only so many nation states on this planet (and they are consolidating, e.g. Euro), but the number of decentralized digital currencies is potentially unlimited.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="15" LastEditorUserId="15" LastEditDate="2011-08-30T22:50:02.553" LastActivityDate="2013-08-30T21:39:32.373" Title="Will forks and alternative block chains cause hyper-inflation of decentralized digital money?" Tags="&lt;economy&gt;&lt;money-supply&gt;&lt;inflation&gt;&lt;alternatives&gt;&lt;currencies&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="4" />
  <row Id="94" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="91" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:23:41.457" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is from my answer on &lt;a href=&quot;https://money.stackexchange.com/questions/9395/how-does-someone-get-bitcoins/9399#9399&quot;&gt;Money.SE&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can set up your computer to mine for Bitcoins, you can exchange goods and services for Bitcoins, or you can purchase Bitcoins on an exchange. Some people will trade their programming or web design services for Bitcoins; others sell goods like alpaca socks in exchange for Bitcoins. The exchanges operate similarly to forex in that someone can trade say USD for Bitcoins (instead of trading USD for Euros or British pounds). According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoincharts.com/markets/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Charts&lt;/a&gt;, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mtgox.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Mt. Gox&lt;/a&gt; exchange has by far the highest volume, but in recent months &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tradehill.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Trade Hill&lt;/a&gt; has gained some ground.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for mining, computer performance matters as well as the &quot;difficulty.&quot; The difficulty in mining fluctuates so that it becomes harder as the collective mining power increases. Mining is set up so that someone earns a block of 50 Bitcoins on average several times an hour (but this reward will decrease with time such that only 21 million are ever created). You can't ever make progress towards mining a block of 50; mining is an inherently random process. It's possible to successfully mine two blocks in short succession only to have a huge gap before successfully mining another block.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I should note that CPU mining is essentially pointless right now. On average it would take several years even for top-end CPUs to successfully mine a block. GPU mining (where the processor built into graphics cards is used) is what is popular now. Even so, it would take on average a long time to generate a block even with several GPUs. As such, many miners join mining pools where everyone shares credit when anyone successfully mines a block. This serves to decrease the variance and is will lead to a more regular flow of Bitcoins instead of long gaps followed by blocks of 50.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="38" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:25:30.827" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:23:41.457" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="96" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="85" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:24:34.487" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;From a theoretical point of view, the interesting part of bitcoin is that it lacks a central issuing authority (often called a mint in the crypto-currency literature). In terms of security an anonymity of users, it does not have particularly strong features. Refer to answers on the following two questions for more info:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cstheory.stackexchange.com/q/7145/1037&quot;&gt;https://cstheory.stackexchange.com/q/7145/1037&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://crypto.stackexchange.com/q/508/617&quot;&gt;https://crypto.stackexchange.com/q/508/617&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="46" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:48:25.933" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:24:34.487" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="97" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="88" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:25:39.420" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;While security is certainly an arms race, the trick that makes bitcoin future-proof is that it's an open source project and we can all actively participate in that arms race. If SHA-256, RIPEMD-160 or ECDSA (the hashing and encryption algorithms behind bitcoin) are ever broken or crippled, we can simply change the client to use whatever &quot;new hotness&quot; replaces them. Since protocols are seldom completely crippled in one fell swoop and there are three protocols that would have to be broken to trivialize bitcoin theft it's quite likely that we'll be able to swap out &quot;crippled&quot; protocols quickly without sacrificing much security.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:25:39.420" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="98" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="85" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:25:46.290" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;The thing that separates Bitcoin from other cryptocurrencies is the amount of computing power the network has. It is extremely difficult to 'overtake' the network because it would be costly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wouldn't say it has the 'best' design aspect to it as something catastrophic as a price crash would cause miners to pull out. It might take months or weeks for the difficulty to get back on par. Transactions will be super slow, as there are few miners to solve the blocks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Something like &lt;a href=&quot;http://solidcoin.info/&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot;&gt;SolidCoin&lt;/a&gt; fixes this problem, I really like the twice daily difficulty adjustments as it prepares the network for something Bitcoin might be prone for.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="63" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:25:46.290" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="99" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="88" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:28:43.857" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin makes mining coins progressively harder, and has a max cap on the total number of coins that will eventually be available. This makes the mining mechanism future proof.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In terms of producing fake transactions and thus double spending or stealing money, you are competing against the network of users, and thus must have more computing power than the rest of the network. If all users increase in computing power at about the same rate, then cheating is prevented. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="46" LastActivityDate="2011-08-30T22:28:43.857" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="100" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="91" CreationDate="2011-08-30T22:28:59.057" Score="63" Body="&lt;h1&gt;Exchanges&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can use an online exchange such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitstamp.net&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;BitStamp&lt;/a&gt; for US dollars, as well as many others for dollars, and other currencies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Buying_bitcoins&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;the wiki&lt;/a&gt; for a full list of ways to buy bitcoins.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1&gt;Brokerage Services&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Brokerage services allow you to buy or sell directly from them instead of relying on a third party to offer the trade with the exchange just taking a cut. One such service is &lt;a href=&quot;https://coinbase.com&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Coinbase&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1&gt;Local / In Person&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can use tools such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://localbitcoins.com&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;localbitcoins.com&lt;/a&gt; to find people near you who will trade cash for bitcoins. &lt;em&gt;(Note, however, that localbitcoins strongly encourages you to use their service despite the fact bitcoin does not require using a 3rd party to do in person transactions)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1&gt;IRC and Remote Trades&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can use &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoin-otc.com&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;bitcoin-otc&lt;/a&gt;'s web of trust system to improve the likelihood of a successful long distance trade.  This could help you do trades with people you find on &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/IRC_channels&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;IRC channels&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Forum&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1&gt;Hardware Mining&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mining bitcoins is very technical, and not for many people.  Unless you already have the hardware and technical skill to set it up I would not recommend mining as a way to get bitcoins.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1&gt;Accept Bitcoin&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I believe by far the best way to get bitcoins is to provide goods and services for bitcoin.  This stimulates the bitcoin economy which in turn makes the bitcoins you receive more valuable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4774" LastEditorUserId="56611" LastEditDate="2019-05-08T20:17:01.650" LastActivityDate="2019-05-08T20:17:01.650" CommentCount="9" />
</posts>